Ayoub Mouloua

Cybersecurity Consultant

 Casablanca, Morocco

 ■ contact@ayoub0x1.me

 +212645469366

 ■ Moroccan
 ⊕ B
 in ayoub0x1

 ayoub0x1

 ayoub0x1#4552

 ¥ Ayoub0x1

 https://app.hackthebox.com/profile/803489

 k https://ayoub0x1.me

₽ PROFILE

Skilled Cybersecurity student with expertise in risk management, unauthorized access, viruses, managing networks, server administration, deploying and monitoring SIEM, and a wide range of vulnerabilities and threats. Well-versed in direct and remote analysis with strong critical thinking, communication, and people skills.

EDUCATION

42 Associate degree, 1337, 1337 school
IT training in several fields: Information security, programming, networking...

Sep 2019 – present

English literature, *Moulay Ismail University* English Studies as a second major

Meknes, Morocco

Sep 2021 - present

Khouribga, Morocco

Baccalaureate, *Manfalouti high school*Baccalaureate degree in physics and chemistry

Sep 2016 – Jun 2019 Meknes, Morocco

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Cybersecurity Consultant, CapValue

• External & Internal Penetration Testing

Jun 2022 – present Casablanca, Morocco

- Web Application Penetration Testing
- Mobile Application Penetration Testing
- Report writing

Bug Bounty Hunter, HackerOne

Apr 2020 – present Remote

Participated in many public and private bug bounty programs through the responsible disclosure of security vulnerabilities in various web technologies and applications to high-profile organizations. Some statistics include but are not limited to:

• Found and Reported several security vulnerabilities and got fixed.

Over 20 acknowledgments were received (U.S. Dept Of Defense, AT&T, IBM, Semrush, Moneybird, Automattic, Hyatt Hotels, etc.).

• Reference: hackerone.com/ayoub0x1

SKILLS

Programming & Scripting • • • • • Web Penetration Test

C/C++/Python/Bash Manual/Automation Audit, vulnerability assessment

 Networking
 SIEM / SOC

 Routing, Network security
 Elastic stack, Prometheus

■ PUBLICATIONS

CVE-2022-2365, zadam

Description: CWE-79 Improper Neutralization of Input During Web Page Generation ('Cross-site Scripting')

Product: zadam/trilium

Cisco

Versions Affected: <0.53.3: affects versions prior to 0.53.3

(3) LANGUAGES

Arabic $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$ English $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$

(2) CERTIFICATES

Introduction to Cybersecurity

Networking Essentials

Cisc

contact@ayoub0x1.me 1/1